riteaidonlinestore.com 2018-10-10

# Online Privacy & Security Policy – Rite Aid

At Rite Aid we to provide you with advanced health care solutions. The personal and medical information that we receive from you is necessary for us to help you maintain your health. Your online privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy applies only to activities conducted and personal information collected on this Riteaid.com website.

## What Information We Collect

We collect personal information you provide when using the Riteaid.com website. Your name, password, home address, medical information, e-mail address and date of birth are examples of personally identifiable information. This information is necessary, for example, to respond to your questions, provide you additional healthcare information and coupons or process your order.

## Information Automatically Collected

We automatically receive and collect certain types of information whenever you visit the Site. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies" and Web beacons (described below) and obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our Site. This information includes the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer, your browser software and operating system, your web server, the date and time you access our Site, session information (such as download errors and page response times), information about your viewing, search and purchase history and information about the referring URL and the URL clickstream to, through, and from our Site. We use this information to monitor the usage and performance of our Site, to enhance our customers' search and shopping experiences and to determine aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns. Please note that we do not respond to or grant any requests by users of our Website not to track or collect personally identifiable information.

When you visit Riteaid.com, you will be assigned a "cookie", which is a small text file stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies store your preferences and settings for a particular website and use them the next time you visit.

Most Internet browsers permit you to erase or block cookies. Refer to your browser instructions or help screens to assist you in these processes: preventing your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Please note that cookies permit you to take full advantage of Riteaid.com features and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

We may also use technologies, such as cookies, to provide you with certain online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of cookies used for certain Rite Aid online advertising, [click here](http://dtmc.riteaid.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=61838&cname=Rite%20Aid&cmagic=21ddd6&clogo=61838.png&loc=us&lang=en-us "TextLink-click here").

## How We Use Your Information

The personal and medical information we receive from you enables us to provide you individualized customer service. That customer service may include messaging with Rite Aid pharmacists, providing healthcare information, special coupons and product offers, and administering contests, surveys or promotions. We may occasionally send useful information to you by e-mail, including new products and when specials or promotions become available.

We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties. We share personal information with third parties who perform services on our behalf. These third parties are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements. We also share the personal information we obtain with our affiliates and subsidiaries. In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials based on a lawful disclosure request, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual fraudulent or illegal activity. We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation).

You may decline to receive any additional e-mails concerning new products and services by emailing us or calling 1-800 RITE AID (1-800-748-3243) and we will remove your name from the mailing list. You also have the right not to disclose your medical history to us. We encourage you to provide the information so that we can assist you with your health care.

## Links to Other Sites

We may provide links to other sites that we believe offer our customers useful products and services. We do not make any endorsement of or representation or warranty regarding linked sites or their content since they are not controlled by Rite Aid. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or security procedures of these links. We suggest you review a linked site's privacy and security policy before providing any information.

## Updating your Personal Information

You can review and update any of the information that you have given us by emailing us or calling 1-800 RITE AID (1-800-748-3243). Our customer care staff will update your information.

## Security

Riteaid.com encrypts your personal and medical information as it is transmitted over the Internet.

## Minors

If you are a registered user of the Site under 18, you or your guardian may request that Rite Aid remove any content or information that you may have posted on our Internet Web site, or any online service, online application, or mobile application, including your name, address, mobile or home phone, gender and date of birth. If you choose to request that Rite Aid remove any such content or information, you may do so by visiting riteaid.com/ContactUs to email or chat live with a customer care agent, calling customer care at 1-800-RITEAID (748-3243), updating your wellness+ profile or by writing to Rite Aid Corporation P.O. BOX 3165 Attn: Customer Care, Camp Hill, PA 17011-3165. Please note that our removal may not be complete or comprehensive, such as when the content or information has been reposted by a third party.

## Changes to Our Policy

This policy was last updated on December 13, 2017. We reserve the right to modify, change or amend this policy at any time. Please check this policy periodically for changes. Use of this Riteaid.com website after modification of this policy is deemed to constitute your consent to this policy as amended.

Updated March 29, 2018
